{
    "id": "a6ce87abf8704280a869a6479b6b9890",
    "title": "Would vs. Should",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "If she left office at six, she ……………….. be here soon.",
            "description": "We use should to indicate logical possibility.",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. I write to him?",
            "description": "We use should to ask for a suggestion.",
            "answers": [
                "Would",
                "Should",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She ……………………………. be informed.",
            "description": "We use should to express necessity.",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "would",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You ………………………….. always speak the truth.",
            "description": "We use should to express necessity.",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You …………………………… talk back to your parents.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would not",
                "should not",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………………. bake a cake if I got time.",
            "description": "In the second conditional, we use a past tense in the if-clause and would + infinitive in the main clause.",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………………. be grateful if you could help me.",
            "description": "Both would and should can be used with the first person pronouns with little difference of meaning.",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………. you like some coffee?",
            "description": "Would is used to make an offer sound more polite. ",
            "answers": [
                "Would",
                "Should",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You ………………………… consult a financial advisor before investing your money.",
            "description": "Should is used to tell people what they should do.",
            "answers": [
                "Would",
                "Should",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I knew that I ………………………… quit smoking.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You …………………………… have wished her on her birthday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "would",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You ……………………………. have sent the letter.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}